It's not only her - there is a brother in the family too that has this problem, it's not only her.
I see.
Okay, so no problem. This is a family problem and I will see you..
Watch how the lady receives her deliverance through the prayer of Prophet T. B. Joshua.
Prophet T. B. Joshua is used as a channel of healing and deliverance
where there is sickness and affliction in the lives of these people.
He prays for them, delivering them in the power of the Holy Spirit,
setting them free from their bondages.
Among them is the lady from the USA.
Testimony Time
Church, my name is Susan Chai, this is my mother Jong Su Choi.
We're from the United States and we are Korean.
You're very welcome.
So, our sister says they are originally Korean but living in the United States of America.
So could you share with us your testimony, starting off with the problems
that brought you to The Synagogue Church of All Nations.
When I was 13 years old, I started doing drugs
and started smoking cigarettes and drinking at parties on the weekends at social events.
As I gradually grew older, my addiction became worse.
I started using it at home,
I started doing it in my everyday life routines and it affected my schoolwork,
it affected my family, it affected everyone around me.
Even when I was coming to The SCOAN, I was still smoking,
I was still under the influence of drugs and...
Okay, just before talking about what happened when you came here,
could you tell us how severe this addiction was.
How much of these drugs were you taking every single day?
I was smoking marijuana, doing ecstasy, doing cocaine every single day and my parents sent me
to several treatment facilities but I was unable to get better until I actually came to The SCOAN.
My mother would pray for me every single day but nothing would change me.
I would still go out and party every single day.
I would be talking to guys all the time and I wouldn't focus on my schoolwork or go to work.
I would just concentrate on my well-being as a partygoer and not as a spiritual being.
Okay, could you just give us an example of the type of hard drugs you were taking?
I was taking marijuana, ecstasy and cocaine and I was smoking one to two packs of cigarettes a day.
Okay, when you were under the influence of these drugs,
just give us an example of what happened to you then.
What are the kind of things you would do to yourself?
How would this influence you to misbehave?
I developed a mood disorder where I'd get depressed, anxious and angry at everyone around me,
especially at my mother. I would yell at her every time she would try to interrupt my conversations
or try to tell me to come to eat at the dinner table with the family
or tell me to do something and go somewhere with her.
I would just get frustrated and yell at her.
This affected my family life, my relationships with everyone around me
and my parents even threatened me to send me to a shelter home.
Right before I came here, my sister and I stopped getting along.
She would yell at me every single day.
She would yell at my parents all the time and blame them for my well-being.
I tried to commit suicide several times in the past by suffocating myself,
by choking myself and my mom would hear me cry and she would come to my room,
break the door open and pry the pillow case away from my face.
I started when I was 13 years old and I'm 30 years old now and so it's been 17 years.
17 years. Could you just tell us - where there times that perhaps you would run away from the home,
your parents would be looking for you and you would not be in the house for a long period of time
because you'd be out partying and going to various clubs?
Yes, I wouldn't come home for weeks and nights and my parents would call me
and I wouldn't pick up their phone calls, they would be worried about me.
They would threaten to call the police on me again.
They did that several times.
I would go into the hospital often - maybe like once every six months
I would be in the hospital and I would be sent to facility treatment centers
because of not coming home and out partying and doing drugs all the time.
Okay, and what efforts did you make to try and stop?
Did you ever try, maybe, going to rehabilitation centres?
Just give us an example of the efforts you made to stop.
I did try going to rehab facilities, treatment centres and I also tried a nicotine patch, nicotine gum,
I also tried lozenges, all types of non-smoking aids to help me quit smoking and stop doing drugs,
but nothing helped until I came to The SCOAN.
Okay, and just tell us, each time you'd go to rehab, what would happen when you came out?
I would relapse every time I came out of rehab and all my hospitalizations,
I would go right back in and come right back out.
Just give us an idea of how many times you have gone in and out of rehab because of this.
I went various times in New Jersey in New York - maybe over 20 times.
So people of God, we can understand what our sister is saying.
More than 20 times she has gone to rehabilitation centers in an attempt to stop
the intoxicating influence of these drugs, cigarettes, alcohol,
but any time she went to the rehabilitation centres upon returning back home
she would fall straight back into the same trap and return with this addiction.
So sister, could you just tell us what actually happened that led you to come to The SCOAN?
My mother heard that The SCOAN heals those who are sick through the man of God -
my mum had heard about it through a friend, Shelly, and we came together two weeks ago.
She left earlier. On behalf of Prophet T. B. Joshua, my mother and I stayed
so I can give this testimony to the world and to those
who are going through the same thing as I was going through.
Before your mum's friend told her about The SCOAN, did you yourself have any idea about the church?
Did you know about The SCOAN or Emmanuel TV?
No, I did not.
I just thought that I was coming to another revival but I didn't know I would find freedom in Christ.
So, your mum just brought you here; you had no knowledge of what was going to happen?
Now, when you arrived, what was your condition when you arrived in the church?
I was still smoking cigarettes,
I was just thinking about drinking a beer,
I was thinking about doing drugs,
until on Sunday, I met the man of God and he prophesied that I was sick
and there's someone in the family who is sick as well.
Since then, I knew that I would be healed.
Amen, let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ.
We saw that after that prophecy, the man of God then prayed for you in the power of the Holy Spirit.
Can you describe what happened when he prayed for you?
As soon as the man of God prayed for me, the spirit of anger left my body.
I felt a weight lifted off my shoulders and off my body
and the whole injury on the right side of my body lifted off and is healed.
My vision is a lot clearer.
I'm able to speak clearer,
to have a conversation with my parents in a mannerly way,
rather than yelling and screaming and being frustrated at them as I was before.
And that urge to take alcohol, drugs, cigarettes - ever since that touch,
just tell us the changes you've seen in your life in that area.
Ever since I was delivered by the man of God, I no longer have the urge
to smoke cigarettes or do drugs or drink alcohol.
I'm healed. Praise God.
Hallelujah. Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ one more time.
We saw there how Jesus Christ touched our sister at the point of her need and completely delivered her.
Sister, we can actually see some of those cigarettes in front of you.
Could you just describe to us what it is we are seeing here and what you can say about these?
These are the cigarettes that were confiscated while I was here at The SCOAN during the week of my stay.
Prophet T. B. Joshua accommodated us here, when we came from the States.
We didn't have an invitation, but he let us stay here for two-and-a-half weeks now.
He's been praying for us, he's been watching over us and he's been doing everything
in his power for me to get healed and for me to remain healed.
Amen; thank You, Jesus Christ.
So, our sister's explaining that the packets of cigarettes
we're actually seeing in front, were what she brought with her from the United States,
but since the deliverance she received, she has completely stopped taking them.
She formerly took one to two packets every day aside from taking hard drugs,
but since that divine touch from Jesus Christ, she's been completely set free.
So right now, we want to hear a few words from her mother.
Madam, you are very welcome in Jesus' name.
Could you please introduce yourself to us and tell us what can you say about
the testimony that your daughter has just given.
Miss Susan Choi & Mother
Prophecy Testimony
Mrs Jong Su Choi
USA
My mother's name is Jong Su Choi, we're from America, and she says that we're South Korean.
Miss Susan Choi & Mother
Prophecy Testimony
Too much anger, too much joy, funny, too much crying.
She says that I had an anger problem, I had a mood disorder for ten years
and it's been affecting the family and our relationships since then.
Miss Susan Choi & Mother
Prophecy Testimony
Before coming here, my dad and my sister said that it would be our last chance coming to Nigeria.
If I don't get healed and I come back to the States, I will be sent to a shelter if this doesn't work out.
Miss Susan Choi & Mother
Prophecy Testimony
In order for my daughter to be healed, God has provided a way for us to be here today.
Miss Susan Choi & Mother
Prophecy Testimony
Thank You, God!
Thank You, Jesus!
I'm so thankful for my daughter to be healed today.
Thank You, God!
Thank You, Jesus!
Amen, let´s put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
Could you tell us the changes you have seen in your daughter?
Tell us her condition before the prayer and the changes after the prayer.
Miss Susan Choi & Mother
Prophecy Testimony
Mental problem.
Miss Susan Choi & Mother
Prophecy Testimony
My parents were about to get divorced because of my mental Issues and my mood disorder,
where I would get very angry.
I would get very joyous, I would laugh and cry.
My dad couldn't handle the fact that I was sick, so he wanted to divorce my mother.
Miss Susan Choi & Mother
Prophecy Testimony
My mum says that now, after I've been prayed for and I'm healed,
I can sleep well, I can eat well, and I'm happy in Christ's name and she's very happy about that.
Amen, let´s put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
So, I hope, people of God, we are understanding what our mother is saying.
The condition of our sister here, her daughter, was so critical
that it reached the point where her parents were about to divorce because of her situation.
They had even given them an ultimatum;
her father had given her an ultimatum that if she returned from Nigeria and did not change,
she would be sent to a homeless shelter.
That is, denied as their child because of this severe addiction to drugs,
cigarettes and alcohol that was bringing shame and disgrace to the family.
But today, mother and daughter are standing here free,
delivered and completely restored after an encounter with Jesus Christ.
Let's put our hands together one more time for Jesus.
So, our mother, we'd like to ask you right now - what is your advice to viewers,
especially to those who may have children who are experiencing such an addicition?
Miss Susan Choi & Mother
Prophecy Testimony
My mom wants to give the advice that God is glorified throughout the earth
and that He does not want you to suffer.
He wants you to be rejoiced through His Word.
Amen.
Amen, let´s put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
So now, for our sister who actually received this incredible deliverance and freedom,
we'd like to ask you sister right now -
what is your own word of advice to viewers around the world,
especially those who may be under the influence of such drugs, alcohol, cigarettes;
as someone that has passed through that and today is free - what is your advice?
For me to have freedom in Christ, it shows that God is able and He does not give up on you.
He still loves you and forgives you, no matter who you are, no matter what you do.
Amen, let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ one more time.
And finally sister, these cigarettes we're seeing here -
what do you want to do right now, that you are delivered?
I don't even want to look at it.
Miss Susan Choi & Mother
Prophecy Testimony
TT: Jacqueline Margaret 07/04/18
RV ROBERT BEGIER 13/07/2018
RV2 MEL FLOWERS 25/07/2018